Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 71st Session, 1957-1991; 6
  - Topical, 1957-1991; 6
    - Utilities, General, 1987-1988 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Utilities, Houston Lighting and Power, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Utilities, Interest Groups and Consumers, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Utilities, Interexchange Carriers and State Telecommunications Policy, 1989 January (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Utilities, International Telecharge Inc. Alternate AOS Proposal, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Utilities, Organizations in Support of the Alternate Operator Services (AOS) Bill, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Utilities, Other States, 1985-1989 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Utilities, Other States’ Public Service Commissions, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Utilities, Plain Old Telephone Service, 1988, undated (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Utilities, Plain Old Telephone Service Conference, 1988 December (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Utilities, Proceedings S.B. 229, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Utilities, Protection Against AOS Bill, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, Public Utility Commission, AOS, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Utilities, Public Utility Commission Cost Forecasting, 1989, undated (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Utilities, Public Utility Commission Local Exchange Carriers, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Utilities, Public Utility Commission Regulation, 1988-1989 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Utilities, Public Utility Commission Status of Telecommunications Competition, 1989 January (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Utilities, Regulation of AOS Providers, Senate Bill Preliminary Draft and Notes, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - Utilities, Related to S.B. 1757, 1988-1989 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Utilities, S.B. 444 Substantive Rule 23.27, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Utilities, Report on Alternative Operator Services (AOS), 1988 July 11 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications Carrier Regulation: S.B. 229, and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications General, 1986-1989 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications General, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, Texas Long-Range Telecommunications Plan, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Utilities, Texas v. Public Utility Commission, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Water Resources, Clear Creek Water Company Complaints, 1987-1988 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Water Resources, Covington, 1981-1988 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Water Resources, Sunset Review, undated (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Workers Compensation, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Workers Compensation, Articles and News Clippings (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Workers Compensation, Articles and News Clippings (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Workers Compensation, Background Research, 1988, undated (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Workers Compensation, Examination of Selected Insurance Issues Report, 1988 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Workers Compensation, Perspectives and Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Workers Compensation, Professional Athletes, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Workers Compensation, Research Papers of the Joint Select Committee, State Profiles, 1988 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Workers Compensation, Related to Committee Review, 1989, undated (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Workers Compensation, Self-Funded Insurance, 1988 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Workers Compensation, Legal Matter Information (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Workers Compensation, Legal Matter Information (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Workers Compensation, State Board of Insurance, 1988-1989 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Workers Compensation, Summary of Research Papers of the Joint Select Committee, 1988 October (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Workers Compensation Information, 1989-1990 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Workers Compensation Law (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Workers Compensation Law (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Workers Compensation Reform, Articles and Related Material, 1989-1990 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Workers Compensation Reform, Senate Deliberations, 1989-1990 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Administrative, 1988-1990; 7
    - Appointment of Chair of Public Utility Commission, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Column “Senator Chet Edwards Reports”, 1988 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Conference Call Information Sheet, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - End of Session Rules, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - Fourth-Called Session Senate Journal, 1990 April (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - Gubernatorial Proclamations, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Legislation Summary and Edwards’ Accomplishments, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter, Chet Edwards, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter, Chet Edwards, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - Post-Session Reviews, News clippings, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - Potential 72nd Session Legislation, 1988-1989 (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - Potential Legislation, undated (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1988-1989 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, TEXCAP, 1988 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Reports and Recommendations to the 71st Legislature, undated (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Senate Bill Analysis Newsletter, 1988 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Senate Committee on Nominations Report, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Session Wrap-Up File, Chet Edwards, 1989-1990 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - Wrap-Up File, Legislative Summary, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 8)